yuwie.com 2011-04-30

# Yuwie | Privacy

**Yuwie.com will never send spam or sell email addresses.**  
**Yuwie.com will never ask you for your password.**   
Last Update: 6/27/07

About Yuwie.com  
Yuwie.com is an online social networking service that allows our members to set up personal profiles for the purpose of linking to friends and sharing information, videos, blogs, and pictures. Yuwie members can view each others' profiles, communicate with old friends and meet new friends on the service. Yuwie also pays our members for based on the amount of activity they have, and based on the activity of their referrals. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. Yuwie members can change their profile information at any time and can control if and how other members and the service communicates with them, and views their information. 

Information Collection and Use by Yuwie.com  
Yuwie.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Yuwie.com service. Yuwie.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. 

Yuwie.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes 

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Yuwie.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Yuwie, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network Users within a personal network communicate on Yuwie.com with each other through the Yuwie.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Yuwie.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, and schools, where users may have attended. 

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their notification settings under the "account settings" area of the control panel. 

From time to time, Yuwie.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on Yuwie.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

You should also be aware that members may reveal other personal information while communicating on other areas of the Yuwie website, such as while participating in discussions on in Yuwic clubs and/or posting information on Yuwie Blogs. This information, in turn, might be viewed by other members or visitors to the Yuwie website who are not members. 

Information Collected and Use  
Yuwie.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Yuwie.com service. Yuwie.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. 

Yuwie.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes 

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Yuwie.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Yuwie, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network Users within a personal network communicate on Yuwie.com with each other through the Yuwie.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Yuwie.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, and schools and/or companies where users may have attended or worked. 

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" settings. 

From time to time, Yuwie.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on Yuwie.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

**PLEASE NOTE THAT, REGARDLESS OF WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION A MEMBER CHOOSES TO INCLUDE IN HIS OR HER PROFILE, OR WHAT LEVEL OF SHARING HE OR SHE CHOOSES, CERTAIN INFORMATION ABOUT EACH MEMBER WILL BE INCLUDED IN THAT MEMBER'S "PUBLIC PROFILE," WHICH IS AN ABBREVIATED VERSION OF A YUWIE PROFILE. THIS INFORMATION INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO: PROFILE PICTURE, AGE, LOCATION, GENDER, DISPLAY NAME, AND PERSONAL QUOTE. PUBLIC PROFILES WILL BE AVAILABLE TO ANY USER OF THE YUWIE WEBSITE, WHETHER OR NOT THE USER IS A MEMBER.**

Chat Rooms, Blogs, Message Boards, and Public Forums   
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, Blogs, Message Boards, Comments or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. 

Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Yuwie will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Yuwie.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Yuwie.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Yuwie reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Yuwie or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

Links  
The Yuwie Website contains links to other websites. This includes links that are placed there by Yuwie (such as in advertisements), as well as by other Yuwie members. Please be aware that Yuwie is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage all members and other users of the Yuwie website to be aware of when they leave our website, and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Yuwie through the Yuwie website. 

Use of Cookies  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on the Yuwie website. However, we do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any Member or other user of the Yuwie website which they did not intentionally submit to us, other than as stated in this Privacy Policy. 

We use both "session ID cookies" and "persistent cookies." We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Note also that members may optionally use a cookie to remember their email in order to automatically log in to our website. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browsers' "help" file; however, please note that, if you reject cookies or disable cookies in your web browser, you will not be able to use the Yuwie website. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Yuwie only, and does not cover the use of cookies by any other party. 

Correcting/Updating or Removing Information  
**REMEMBER THAT YOU CAN CHANGE THE GROUP OF PEOPLE WHO MAY VIEW YOUR PROFILE AT ANY TIME. YOU CAN CHANGE THESE PRIVACY SETTINGS BY GOING TO YOUR CONTROL PANEL AND CLICKING THE "ACCOUNT SETTINGS" LINK. ALSO, YOU CAN ALWAYS CHANGE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU'VE SUBMITTED TO THE YUWIE WEBSITE, INCLUDING THE INFORMATION INCLUDED IN YOUR YUWIE PROFILE, BY CLICKING THE "EDIT PROFILE" LINK ON YOUR YUWIE PROFILE PAGE.**

Changes in Our Privacy Policy  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so members and other users of the Yuwie website are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use members' or other users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify those members and users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

Invite a Friend  
If a Member elects to use our "Invite" feature to invite a friend to become a Member of the Yuwie service, we ask them for the friend's email address. Yuwie will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the site. Yuwie stores this email address for the purpose of automatically adding the respondent to the friends list of the member sending the invitation, and also to send reminders of the invitation. Yuwie will never sell these email addresses or send them any invitations unless it is requested by the member who invited them originally. Any person who receives an invitation may contact Yuwie to request the removal of this information from our database. 

Security  
The Yuwie account of every member is password-protected. Yuwie takes every precaution to protect the information of the members, as well as information collected from other users of the Yuwie website. We use industry standard measures to protect all information that is stored on our servers and within our database. We limit the access to this information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. Be aware that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time 

Email Choice/Opt-out  
Members who no longer wish to receive our weekly email updates or other email notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable email or by logging-in and changing their settings in the "Account Settings" section of the Yuwie website. You can access this page by clicking on the "Control Panel" link in the main menu. 

Third Party Advertising  
We partner with third party ad networks and allow such networks to use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable data for targeting and serving ads. Users can opt-out of this behavioral targeting by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

Members and Users Located Outside of the United States of America  
We have made an effort to protect the personal information of all members and other users of the Yuwie website, and to the extent applicable, we attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws. If you are unsure whether this privacy policy is in conflict with the applicable local rules where you are located, you should not submit your personal information to the Yuwie website. **IN ADDITION, IF YOU ARE LOCATED WITHIN THE EUROPEAN UNION, YOU SHOULD NOTE THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, THE LAWS OF WHICH MAY BE DEEMED BY THE EUROPEAN UNION TO HAVE INADEQUATE DATA PROTECTION**. Members and other users of the Yuwie website located in countries outside of the United States of America who submit personal information do thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that information to and/or storage of the information in the United States of America. 

Contacting Yuwie  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, Yuwie's privacy practices, or your dealings with Yuwie, contact us.
